Okay.
Hey, what the fuck?
- Hey, hey.
- Easy. Don'’t move.
You'’re making
big mistake, you know that?
Shut the fuck up.
- Let'’s go.
- Fuck.
[Joel] Get the door.
Shut the fuck up.
Watch the fucking jacket,
man. It'’s new.[Joel] Shut the fuck up!
Listen to me.
You alert your brother
and I shoot you in
the back of the head,
you understand me?
Okay. You'’re the boss.
Slow.
Yo, yo, yo!
You remember
my pumpkin frappé, huh?
Don'’t! Don'’t.
Touch it and he'’s
fucking dead. Hands up!
Jesus Christ,
you dumb motherfucker.
Do you know who we are?
Yeah, I know who you
fucking are. Last January,
the two of you shot an
innocent mother and a kid.
Killed '’em. In Newark.
Oh, yeah? Says who?
Who the fuck are you, huh?
I brought something
to give you.
Uh-huh?
But you have to watch
what I'’m doing.
You watching?
Oh! No!
No! No!
Oh, shit. No, no, no.
No, no, no. Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
No, don'’t die.
Don'’t die, don'’t die!
Fuck! Fuck. Look at me.
Look at me, you motherfucker,
you can'’t die! You can'’t die!
It needs somebody
to fucking pass to.
If you die, it won'’t
fucking work. Look at me!
Stay alive, you piece of shit.
Stay alive, you piece of shit!
Oh, G-- No.
Oh, no.
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck!
Now it has no one
to pass to, fuck!
Fuck. Fuck.
No, no, no!
- Who the fuck are you?
- No one.
- I'’m Lewis.
I'’m no one. I'’m no one.
- I'’m literally no one.
- What the fuck you doing here?
- Don'’t shoot me.
- Answer me!
What the fuck
are you doing here?
I just buy from them, okay?
I fucking hate those guys.
I hate them, too!
I fucking hate them,
especially him!
Please, don'’t shoot me.
I didn'’t know
anybody else was here.
Okay, fuck it.
I didn'’t fucking know
anybody else was here!
I fucked this whole thing up.
I fucked this whole thing up
and I'’m sorry.
This wasn'’t meant for you.
What?
What wasn'’t meant for me?
- I'’m sorry.
- What? What are you-- Fuck.
What are you sorry for?
Fuck.
- I'’m sorry.
- What?
Yo,
who the fuck is that?
Oh, shit.
Ah!
Fuck!
Who has the goddamned key?
Come on! Fuck!
No, no,
- no, no, don'’t shoot!
- Shit.
Fuck! Alexi
- and Yev are fucking dead!
- Oh, fuck.
Get that piece of shit!
Open it!
Break the fucking door down!
Break it! Break it!
Go! Go!
Move! Move!
Shoot the motherfucker!
Problem solved.
♪ I already grieved you ♪
♪ So say what you want, but ♪
♪ This time
I don'’t believe you ♪
♪ While you been
Talking circles ♪
♪ Every time you got caught ♪
♪ I already grieved you
Grieved you ♪
Thank you, everybody.
Now, nearly one year ago,
singer/songwriter
and pop superstar Skye Riley
was fighting for her life
after being injured in
a car accident.
An accident that also
tragically took the life
of actor Paul Hudson.
Today, for her first
public interview
since the accident,
ladies and gentlemen,
the one and only Skye Riley.
Oh, my God, Drew!
Thank you so much
for having me.
So happy to be doing this
with you.
I mean, I have got to say
that you look incredible
in person.
-  Oh, my gosh. As do you.
- Your hair-- I'’m obsessed.
Oh, my God. My hair. I was
just trying something new.
I'’m not sure if
- I'’m pulling it off.
- Um, I-- What do we think?
[Skye] Oh, my God.
Well, I think
you have your answer.
Now you'’ve announced
new tour dates... Yes.
...actually kicking off
right here in New York City
next week. Is this
an emotional comeback?
Yes, a lot of different
emotions, you know, with
this one.
A year ago, you had
- just won a Grammy.
- Mm-hmm.
You were in the middle
- of a big world tour.
- Mm.
And then you hit
this rough patch.
"Rough patch" might
be generous.
I was wondering
if you could share anything
from that period of your life.
I was dealing with
a lot of stress and pressure
from the demands of the tour.
And I should have
asked for help, but
instead I drowned it all out
with...
drugs and alcohol
and a lot of bad decisions.
And I let myself get
completely out of control.
And actually, I want to
take this opportunity
to apologize to my fans,
my loved ones, my team.
Everyone who was counting on me
and supporting me.
I let you all down and...
I promise
that will never
happen again.
So, thank you.
You were in the hospital.
When you got out,
what has the time been like
between then and now?
I spent a lot of time
looking inward.
Relearning how to
appreciate life sober.
And I'’m...
I'’m just so grateful
for this second chance,
and I don'’t want to waste it.
Car'’s waiting right
outside by the curb.
There'’s a bit of a crowd.
Skye!
- My name is Ashley.
- So nice to meet you.
That went really well.
- You were perfectly graceful.
- Yeah.
Skye, you'’ve got
Instagram and TikTok
seriously blowing up
right now.
You'’re trending number two
on Twitter. I mean, you should
really be so proud...
♪ There'’s no medicine ♪
♪ To change me ♪
♪ I'’m goin'’ crazy! ♪
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
♪ Lost in a spiral ♪
♪ Keep making old mistakes
Again ♪
♪ Uh-oh, gimme a new brain ♪
♪ Stuck in a cycle ♪
♪ If I don'’t stop
I'’ll end up dead ♪
♪ Can you change my thoughts?
Can you make '’em clean?♪
♪ Can you clear my head?
Can you fix my dreams?♪
♪ Doctor, I'’m goin'’ insane ♪
♪ I'’ve got a bad mind
Give me a new brain ♪
♪ I'’ve got a sweet tooth
For bad decisions
My mind is wired wrong ♪
Good.♪ It won'’t take long
Till I'’m the villain ♪
♪ Put me under
Anything you can uncover ♪
♪ Make me forget my wonders
Make me forget--♪
Eyes up!
♪ Do you think
Someone could save me?♪
♪ Curious, can you erase me? ♪
♪ There'’s no medicine
To change me ♪
♪ I'’m goin'’ crazy! ♪
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
♪ Lost in a spiral ♪
Are you okay?
What happened?
Are you hurt?
Yep, I'’m fine.
I'’m fine. I think
I just took a weird step.
Let'’s take a break, everyone.
Can we get some ice?
Anton, I'’m fine. I'’m fine.
- Skye.
- Can we please just go again?
- I want to get it right, okay?
- Okay.
- Let'’s go.
- Let'’s go again.
-  Line up!
- Rewind it.
- Yep.
- Back to one.
Music.
♪ Give me a new brain ♪
♪ I'’ve got a sweet tooth ♪
Shit!
One second!
Yeah, come in.
Hey.
You okay?
- You ready to go?
- Yeah, Mom.
I just need a minute.
You should feel really good
about today.
I know.
I do.
Good.
We'’re ready whenever you are.
Final rehearsal is
confirmed for Wednesday.
So we'’ll be at the venue
first thing in the morning.
You have a fitting,
photo shoot,
then stage walk-throughs,
then a fan meet-and-greet.
Please go straight to bed
when you get home.
It'’s going to be a long day.
Oh, and reminder:
Darius gets in tomorrow.
He'’s gonna be here for opening.
I want him
to feel the love, please.
The label is advancing
a lot of money on this tour.
Have I ever not been
good with Darius?
Darius adores you, obviously.
Just want you to remember
who'’s paying the bill.
Hey, straight to bed, Skye.
Good night.
Miss Riley.
Hey.
What the fuck, Lewis?
- What do you want from me?
- Vicodin! Just Vicodin.
Just for pain,
- same as last time.
- Fuck that!
Skye Riley isn'’t just gonna
suddenly show up here.
Your text
said to come over.
- What?
- What? What?
I don'’t--
I don'’t remember texting that.
How come I don'’t remember
texting that?
- Oh, fuck.
- I don'’t know.
Just get the fuck off me.
Get the fuck off me!
Oh. Oh, shit.
Holy shit, I'’m sorry.
I'’m sorry.
I am having the worst week.
The worst!
Lewis... what was
with the sword?
Uh, what? What sword?
Oh, that sword.
I feel--
I'’m so sorry about that.
I cannot be too careful
right now. Okay?
I am in the middle of some
genuinely fucking freaky shit.
Okay? I'’m talking like
fucking scary,
fucking haunted-house shit,
you know?
Yo...
do you believe in, like,
weird stuff?
- Yeah, I'’m gonna go.
- What? No, no, no!
No, please stay.
Please stay. What am I doing?
What am I doing?
Skye fucking Riley'’s here
and Lewis is being fucking
crazy?
I am so stoked to see you.
I am pumped. Come on. Come in.
I will chill. Be my guest.
Please take a seat.
Make yourself at home.
I'’m sorry about the mess.
You said you, uh, wanted...
what was it?
You want Vicodin? Right?
- Yeah.
- I got you. I got you.
Want anything else?
I got banger ketamine.
I got really good
fucking Molly. I got some...
- I don'’t know what this is.
- No, dude, just the
Vicodin for my back.
Oh, right, your back.
Ouch. That sucks.
I hate that.
Okay, well, you chill,
and I'’ll be right back.
You chill and I'’ll be
right back, okay?
I'’ll be right back. Mmm.
- Oh, my God.
- You smell good.
I missed you!
Skye fuckin'’ Riley, dude!
Vicodin. Vicodin.
What the fuck are you thinking?
...could still have
some freezing
or subfreezing temps...
What the fuck?
Ah, shit.
Here'’s how we see
everything coming together.
The cold air stays in place.
...north of the area...
Freddy. It'’s some snow.
I mean, this is not a huge
storm. It'’s not, you know,
an ultra-dangerous situation
out there. It'’s our first
snow of the season.
Over in pop culture
news, singer/songwriter
Skye Riley is back,
nearly one year after
she was hospitalized
in a car crash
that tragically killed
actor Paul Hudson.
Hudson had been
driving the vehicle
after the high-profile couple
had left a private party
where both were reportedly
seen intoxicated.
Yeah, you know,
that accident occurred
while Riley was in the middle
of a blockbuster tour
and at the time,
there was speculation
surrounding Riley'’s substance abuse.
Especially after candid photos
of the singer
went viral just two weeks
before the acc--
Hey, uh, Lewis, I kind
of have a really early
morning tomorrow, so...
Lewis!
This fucking guy.
Lewis, what the fuck, man?
Lewis!
Swear to God, if you'’re
fucking with me, dude...
- Jesus!
- Skye!
What the fuck
is wrong with you, Lewis?
Where the fuck
did you come from?
What?
- Oh! No! No! No!
- What? What is it?
Get the fuck away from me!
- Get the fuck away from me!
- What the fuck is happening?
No! No!
Oh, shit.
Lewis? Lewis? Fuck!
What do I do, Lewis, do I call
an ambulance? Fuck. Shit.
Lewis, Lewis! Lewis?
What the fuck?
Lewis?
Fuck. Shit!
Shit.
You fuckin'’ OD'’ing, man?
Shit! Fuck!
Lewis?
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
What do you think, Skye?
Skye?
Hey! Are you paying attention?
What?
Yeah.
This stuff is important.
- I'’m listening.
- Are you okay?
-  You look exhausted.
- Wow, thanks, Mom.
It'’s really important for you
to stay on top of
your sleep schedule.
- Joshua, grab her a water.
- I'’m fine.
I want you to have
someone around to help
out with things again.
Have you talked to Gemma
about coming on tour?
Gemma is not gonna want
to hear from me, Mom.
- Have you reached out?
- No, not exactly.
She'’s your best friend. I'’m
sure she'’d be willing to forgive
whatever it was that happened
between the two of you.
You'’re a completely different
- person than you were a year ago.
- Can you please leave it alone?
All I'’m saying is real friends
are hard to come by.
And it was really good for you
when Gemma was around.
I'’d be more than happy to help
out with any personal stuff
Skye might need.
Do you want--
- I don'’t want that.
- You need to stay hydrated.
Will you just stop?
Okay.
No, sorry, not you.
[Skye'’s mom] Come in!
Hi, Darius!
Just wanted to say hi
to my favorite rock star.
I'’d get up and hug you
but I'’m trapped.
- All good. I'’ll come to you.
- Look at you.
- Hey, Elizabeth.
- Hi.
- Hey, Darius.
- Hey, man.
Starting to get
exciting around here.
Oh, my God. I am so excited.
I have a little favor
- to ask of you.
- Sure.
Tomorrow night,
there'’s a fundraising dinner
for Music Inspires Hope.
It'’s a foundation
for underprivileged youth.
Interscope Records has done a
- lot of work with the foundation.
- Wow.
I know this is last-minute,
but I was hoping you'’d
be willing
- to be a special presenter.
- Oh!
I know you'’ve got
a lot on your plate, but
there'’s no arrival carpet,
no press. None of that
annoying stuff.
It'’s purely about the kids.[mouthing] Yes.
Your remarks will be prewritten.
All you have to do is smile
and read from the teleprompter.
How could I say no?
Number three.
Let'’s start with a 70.
All right, Skye.
Loving this.
Can you give me more?
Even more.
More.
"Hey..."
What the fuck?
Fuck this guy, man.
Come on.
Get your shit together.
Jesus!
Can you knock?
We were knocking.
You weren'’t answering.
Why were you screaming?
- I-- I saw a spider.
- Sorry, there'’s
a spider in here?
Tanya says there'’s some
wardrobe issue that you
needed me to look at.
Yeah, I'’m not wearing this one.
I love it. What--
What'’s wrong with it?
Can you show her, please?
The lighting'’s gonna show
- right through this onstage.
- And?
I'’m not trying to show everyone
how fucking disgusting I am.
I think you'’re overreacting
a little bit.
Yeah, Skye, you know what?
I think your scar is badass.
-  It is badass.
- Seriously.
This is honestly
one of your best looks.
I'’m not wearing it.
- There you go.
- Thank you, thank you!
All right,
let'’s grab that photo, yeah?
Can we do matching poses?
Of course.
What are you thinking?
Um, like...
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Twinsies. Super cute.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming out.
- Thank you.
- Who'’s next?
"Too Much For One Heart"
got me through
literally the worst breakup
of my life.
I feel like
you'’re my spirit animal and...
Oh, my gosh,
can I give you a hug?
Oh, my gosh, yes! Aw.
Skye, you got to check out
my SoundCloud.
Oh.[chuckles] Like,
who does your production?
All right, dawg,
let'’s grab that photo now.
-  Nice.
- Oh, can we do one
more vertical?
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
Oh, my God, that'’s...
That was amazing.
Could you sign,
"For Alfredo..."
Alfredo...
"...love...
Skye."
Yeah.
There you go.
All right.
Let'’s take that photo.
I'’m a really big fan.
Oh, thanks for coming out.
I can see you'’re sad
on the inside.
- Sorry, what?
- I could make you happy.
- We would be so happy together.
- Okay, I think we got it.
And you'’re so beautiful.
You have the most
amazing... skin!
- Dude, get the fuck off me!
- Amazing skin!
Skye, I love you!
I love you, Skye! Skye!
Hey, folks, just give us,
like... one quick sec.
You okay?
You need to take a break?
You sure?[sighs] Let'’s just
get through this.
Hey, Skye.
- Everything gravy?
- Yeah, fine.
All right, who'’s next?
Hi. What'’s your name?
That'’s-- That'’s a pretty
cool shirt you got.
You want me to sign it?
Okay.
How about a photo?
Yeah. So sweet.
All right, one, two...
Cheese.
[chuckles] All right.
Now that'’s a good one.
It'’s Gemma. Leave it.
Hi!
Hi, it'’s me. Um...
I was just thinking
about you and, uh...
how much...
how much I want to apologize
about everything.
Anyway, I don'’t know if
you want to talk to me. Um...
Will you call me? Please?
I miss you.
Shit.
Hey![Gemma] Hey.
How have you been?
Pretty good, I guess.
Surprised to hear from you.
I know. Sorry I just
called out of the blue.
No, it'’s okay.
It'’s cool.
Actually, um...
I kind of feel...
...really, uh,
overwhelmed at the moment.
I know it'’s not...
I know it'’s not your problem
and it'’s probably really...
shitty of me to even
be calling you. But, uh...
I don'’t really have anyone
I can talk to right now.
What'’s going on?
Any chance
you'’d want to come over? What, like right now?
Yeah, unless you'’re, you know,
busy or something.
No, I...
Yeah, no, I can come over.
Give me, like, 45.
Perfect. Okay, cool. See you soon.
See you then. Bye.
♪ Got thick skin ♪
♪ I got thick skin
But I'’m hollow ♪
♪ Made up of broken parts ♪
♪ Got a body
But it'’s borrowed ♪
♪ With a shadow for a heart ♪
♪ Is this
How my story'’s told?♪
♪ I get higher till-- ♪
Hello?
Jesus, fuck!
What is happening right now?
Is someone else here?
Skye, what'’s going on?
What the fuck?
Right. So...
I'’m confused.
Oh. Hi to you, too.
How did you get
- here so fast?
- Wait.
Why? What do you mean?
You called me like an hour ago.
An hour?
How you doing, Skye?
I, um...
...didn'’t sleep
last night, and I...
think I had some sort of crazy
lucid-nightmare-fever-dream,
and it scared the...
...scared the crap out of me.
Um... thirsty?
This therapist from my recovery
program she suggested that...
anytime I feel overwhelmed by
the urge to use or get drunk
that I should stop
whatever I'’m doing
and drink
a full glass of water.
It'’s supposed to be some
sort of form of acknowledgement
for what I can
and can'’t control.
Well, it'’s good to see you.
Jesus, Gemma.
I'’m so sorry.
I was a ginormous
fucking asshole.
- I owe you such a huge apology.
- You really do.
I don'’t know why it'’s taken you
like a year to tell me that.
I know. I'’m sorry. I...
I did want to call sooner.
I just didn'’t know
if you would...
forgive me
or if you hated me
and never wanted
to hear from me again.
Okay, apology accepted.
Oh, God.
Fucking love you.
You know that, right?
- Okay.
- Seriously.
You'’re my ride or die.
Okay! Before we start
sucking each other'’s dicks,
what'’s going on?
Why are you being so weird?
I don'’t know.
I'’m such a mess.
Just how messy
are we talking?
Something really bad happened.
You remember Lewis Fregoli?
Lewis Fregoli from high school?
He died in front of me
yesterday.
- What?
- I went to his apartment
to buy Vicodin.
- Skye, what the fuck?
- Just for pain, I swear.
Gemma, I haven'’t
touched alcohol
or coke in a year,
I promise.
But my back
is still fucked.
Since I have a history
of substance abuse,
no one will prescribe me
anything stronger than Tylenol.
You think that maybe
there'’s a reason for that?
Well, I don'’t know
what else to do.
Everyone'’s counting on me.
Okay, just wait.
All right. Go back.
What happened to Lewis?
When I showed up,
there was something off
about him.
Like he was scared
of something.
He started... freaking out
and screaming,
like screaming screaming.
And then he...
grabbed this metal gym weight
from like a bench press...
and then he like...
just smashed
his whole face in with it.
What?
- Ew. Oh, my God. What?
- I didn'’t know what to do.
I just freaked
and ran out, and...
- Gemma, I just left him there.
- Does anyone else know
about this?
- No. Should I tell the police?
- No! Skye, no, listen to me.
If anyone connects you
to a drug dealer'’s death,
the story will take over your
life and fuck up everything.
- And it'’s not your fault.
- I keep seeing
his face everywhere.
- I just feel so fucked up!
- Yeah, no wonder.
I can'’t imagine how scary
that must have been.
Oh, God, I'’m sorry.
I'’m so sorry I'’m laying
all of this on you.
I just...
I don'’t know, I just don'’t
really have anyone to talk to.
You want me to spend the night?
Really? Would you?
I mean, I'’m already here.
Oh, God,
I missed you, bitch.
Help me!
Please someone help!
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Gemma, I'’m so sorry
about everything.
I know, it'’s okay.
I already forgave you.
I don'’t know why
I destroy everything.
I feel like my brain is...
this really fucked-up place,
full of all this
chaos and noise.
And I'’m trapped there
all alone...
...in this darkness.
And I just want
to quiet the noise,
but I don'’t know how.
It'’s because
you'’re a horrible person.
What did you say?
Gemma?
Oh, hey, you'’re up!
What the fuck is happening?
What do you mean?
I made matcha.
Matcha? What?
Wait, it'’s-- it'’s morning?
What time is it?
Fuck! Fuck, I'’m so late!
Why didn'’t you wake me?
I'’m sorry, I didn'’t know.
I don'’t have your schedule.
My mom is gonna
fucking kill me! Aw, shit.
- Can I help you or something?
- Will you come on tour?
- What?
- Come to rehearsal with me today.
Today? I can'’t. I have
a friend'’s thing later on.
What? What-- What friend?
Do you have to go?
Well, yeah,
I made a commitment.
Fuck. Well, then
can you start tomorrow?
I mean, I don'’t know. I sort of
feel like this is like a thing
we should have a conversation
about first.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'’m sorry, I'’m sorry.
There are a hundred people
waiting for just you.
I know! I know!
Hey, Elizabeth.
Look, talent'’s here.
Okay, talent'’s pulling in.
-  Thought we said 8:30.
- I'’m so sorry. It'’s my fault.
But I'’m ready.
I'’m ready, let'’s do this.
Sorry, everyone.
I'’m here. I'’m so sorry.
Sorry.
I need some water
for my daughter.
For my daughter,
I need some water.
I need a waiter
with some water.
♪ I'’ve got a secret to tell you
I think you already know ♪
♪ There'’s something wrong
With me ♪
♪ Bet you can see
It'’s starting to show ♪
♪ I'’m feeling different
In my skin ♪
♪ I feel that something
Is changing ♪
♪ Is it just me
Or are the colors ♪
♪ Melting off
Of the painting?♪
♪ Might be a tragedy ♪
♪ Devastation
Right in front of me ♪
♪ Am I a future disaster
That'’s waiting to happen?♪
♪ That'’s waiting to happen ♪
♪ Like blood on white ♪
♪ Part the sea
You should get out of my way ♪
♪ I'’m holding glass in my hand
And it could break ♪
♪ Something so physical ♪
♪ Made me a cynical disaster
Waiting to happen ♪
♪ Like blood on white satin ♪
♪ It'’s like the switch
Of an engine ♪
♪ I think I broke
All the brakes ♪
♪ Am I defective? Cuz I'’m dying
To make stupid mistakes ♪
♪ Oh, might be a tragedy ♪
Oh, fuck!
God!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
Oh, fuck, fuck!
Fuck!
Oh, God.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Are you okay?
My leg!
- What happened? What'’s wrong?
- My--
Who was that?
One of you was out of place
and knocked me over!
Who was it?
Skye, I don'’t think
that'’s what happened.
Do not tell me
what I just experienced, Anton!
I'’m not.
I'’m just saying
that from where I was watching,
I didn'’t see anyone
out of place.
Skye!
- What happened?
- Where is Joshua?
Christ, what did you do?
Hey. Everything okay?
Can I get you anything?
What the fuck
is your problem, man?
- Sorry, what?
- Are you fucking with me?
I have no idea what you'’re
- talking about, I swear.
- He trashed my dressing room!
- What? Wha-- No, I didn'’t!
- I fucking saw you, Joshua!
Skye! I... Skye.
I would never,
ever do something
like that to you, okay?
Like, come on.
What reason would I have?
- Fuck you. Fuck you!
- Okay.
Fuck you! Fuck you, Joshua!
- Fuck you!
- All right. That'’s enough.
Mom, you need to believe me.
He did this!
- He fucking did this!
- You need to cool off.
You'’re not actually
taking his side?
I am on your side,
okay? Always.
But Joshua has been
with me the entire day.
What? What are you
even talking about?
I don'’t even care what happened
in here, we'’ll get it fixed.
I just need you to...
...tell me the truth.
I'’m gonna ask you something...
...and I want you
to be honest with me.
Skye? Are you using again?
What?
Nobody has to know.
You just have to
tell me the truth.
Oh, my God, no!
I am not using again, Mom.
You want me
to take a drug test?
Okay.
I believe you. Um...
What'’s going on?
I don'’t know! I don'’t know!
I just--
Fuck, I feel crazy all the time.
Everything'’s going wrong.
Nobody will fucking listen
to me and everyone fucking
hates me.
Oh, come on, do you hear
yourself? Everybody loves you.
We'’re all here for you. We'’re
here because we believe in you.
We believe in this tour.
I think doing this tour
was a huge mistake. It'’s--
It'’s too much.
- I'’m not-- I'’m not ready for it.
- Okay, you know what?
We'’re gonna, um, look at the
book tonight. Look at the dates,
carve out some time for you
to decompress before opening.
But right now
you need to pull it together
and get back out there.
Because we need to be on time
for Darius'’s foundation event.
Fuck, no. Mom, please
don'’t make me do that.
I can'’t get out on stage
in front of a bunch
of people tonight.
- Skye.
- Mom, you'’re not--
Fuck, you'’re not
listening to me!
I am not in the headspace
to put on a fucking dress
and play dancing monkey
in front of a room
- full of strangers!
- Darius is counting on you
to be there, okay?
You gave him your word.
You are a woman
who keeps her word.
You are not gonna cancel
on a commitment
to underprivileged youth
right before launching a tour.
Music Inspires Hope
was founded on the idea
that no dream could be too big.
With the help and support
of everyone in this room
and from all of our donors
across the country,
the foundation has been able
to reach more families
this year than ever before.
Thanks to you,
more and more children
every day
are able to make
their wildest dreams a reality.
And now without further ado,
it is my great pleasure
to introduce... Ten seconds.
...a wonderful young artist.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please put your
hands together... I'’ll take that.
...for Skye Riley.
Wow.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'’m Skye Riley,
and I'’m here tonight to...
Uh...
I'’m here tonight to...
Oh, that'’s, uh...
So, how'’s everyone
doing tonight?
Hope you'’re all
enjoying the party.
Uh. Don'’t worry, though.
I'’m sober.
So...
Um...
What can I say about
how music inspires hope?
Well,
music gave me
everything I ever wanted.
Then again, music did almost
kill me, so there'’s that.
Uh... Well, I--
I guess that'’s not fair.
Music didn'’t put
all those drugs up my nose,
I did.
Um...
I-- I think
I'’m supposed to be up here
offering words of inspiration
and advice.
Well, when I think about
what I wish someone would have
told me when I was younger
and first getting started,
I suppose I'’d say
this business is really hard.
And, uh, you'’ll spend years
of your life chasing success
you know, thinking that
when it comes,
it will magically fix,
you know, everything
that'’s bad and wrong about you.
And then you achieve success,
and you realize that
it can'’t fix
the deeply broken person
that you have always been.
And now you can'’t escape
the miserable thing
that you'’ve become,
and one day, you realize
how badly you wish you could
just trade it all just for
one fucking moment of happiness!
Oh.
Sorry about that. Uh...
What I meant to say is:
I hope the next generation
of young artists
finds themselves
truly inspired tonight.
I know I sure am.
And without any further ado,
I'’d like to introduce
our next guest,
a very special person
who surely needs
no introduction:
Paul Hudson.
What?
Why does it say that?
That'’s not--
This-- No. Why did s--
This-- Why did--
What?
No.
No, stay away from me.
Stay away from me!
Paul'’s dead!
You'’re not Paul!
Stop smiling at me!
No, no.
I can hold it. No, no, stop.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Do you see it?
It just stares at me,
smiling.
Skye!
Thank you for agreeing to see--
Wait, what are you doing?
Sending a photo of you to my
friend in case you'’re some
kind of creep.
What? I'’m not a creep.
Yeah, that'’s what
every creep says.
Look, I realize
you'’re super famous,
and I invaded your
privacy. I apologize.
This is also
very weird for me.
- How do you know Lewis?
- I don'’t.
I-- I didn'’t.
I was trying to
contact Lewis to warn him.
Tracked down his address
and went to his apartment.
The front door was unlocked,
and he was already dead inside.
I checked his phone,
and you were the last
person he texted with.
W-What were you trying
to warn him about?
I'’m aware that what
I'’m about to say is going
to sound completely insane,
but Lewis didn'’t kill himself.
He was systematically infected,
possessed and then murdered
by some kind
of metaphysical being.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
If it helps, you might call it
a-- a spirit or a demon.
Maybe. I have no clue
what this thing is!
But it disguises itself
to look like people.
Like smiling people.
But only the person that'’s
been infected by it can see it.
No, that'’s--
that'’s not real. That'’s
some supernatural bullshit.
But you'’ve seen it,
haven'’t you?
That'’s why you'’re still
sitting here.
I--
I don'’t know.
I don'’t know what'’s happening.
I feel like I'’m losing
my goddamn mind!
That'’s precisely
what this thing does to you.
It'’s what it did to Lewis
while it was latched onto him.
It'’s like a parasite
that infects the host
through their mind.
In less than a week,
it drives the host insane.
It'’s like it feeds off
all the bad shit in their head,
and then
once it'’s done feeding,
it forces the host to kill
themself in front of a witness.
And then that witness
becomes the new host.
That'’s how you got it
from Lewis.
It was passed to Lewis
by a cop in Jersey.
That cop was the first one
I tried to contact,
but I guess he went
off the grid.
That cop caught it
from some doctor, who got it
from a patient, who got it
from a college professor.
And the chain
keeps going back.
I'’ve documented all of this.
I can show you.
Why do you even know
all of this?
Because it killed my brother.
My brother was a host
eight people before you.
He tried to tell me
what was happening to him.
But he made it hard
to trust him,
and the stuff he was saying
sounded certifiably crazy.
He begged me for help.
But I didn'’t listen.
And then a few days later...
...I got a call informing me
that he tore his own jaw off
with a crowbar.
Well, have you gone
to the police?[chuckling] And say what?
My brother'’s suicide
was actually caused
by some cosmic evil being
that no one else can see?
The police can'’t
stop this thing anyway.
So I'’m just supposed to wait
until this thing kills me?
No, I want you
- to help me destroy it.
- How?
From what I can tell,
the chain stops
when an infected host dies
in some other way
outside of the being'’s control.
My guess is that,
just like other parasites,
without a living host
it has no way to survive.
It ceases to exist.
So it only stops if--
if I die before it kills me?
Exactly. We need
to kill you first.
What?
Only technically. Look.
There are ways that we can
very safely stop your heart.
That'’ll deprive it
of a living host.
Once it goes,
I can resuscitate your heart
and bring you back.
Are you
out of your fucking mind?
I know it seems extreme.
"Extreme"?
You'’re asking to kill me!
Whoa, hey. Just keep it down.
I don'’t even know you.
I don'’t even know you!
My name is Morris.
I'’m an ER nurse,
and if we don'’t do this,
it'’s gonna kill you
like it killed Lewis
and infect another victim.
Look, I'’ve already got
everything prepared.
We should just go now and
get rid of this thing tonight.
- I can'’t. I can'’t do this.
- You'’re nearly out of time!
This thing has been feeding
on you for three days already!
It'’s already taking control
of your brain, and pretty soon
you won'’t even realize
the ways it'’s manipulating you,
and then it'’ll be too late
to stop it. We have to go
right now.
Is that Skye Riley?
Holy shit. Dude.
That'’s Skye?[onlooker 2] It'’s Skye Riley!
Would you do a quick
- TikTok with us?
- Skye Riley!
I watched that video
where you knocked down that
old lady like fifty times!
That shit was so fucking funny.
Skye!
Skye, can I get your autograph?
Fuck!
No! No!
Don'’t! No!
No! No! No!
No!
Get off!
What?
-  What?
- What?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Are you crying right now?
I'’m-- I'’m not crying. [sniffs]
Are you crying?
Hmm? Huh?
Hey! Hey, I'’m fucking
talking to you!
Are you fucking kidding me?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
What the fuck
is wrong with you, huh?
I don'’t know! I don'’t know!
I don'’t know, Paul.
Why don'’t you tell me,
since I can'’t
do anything right?
Jesus Christ! I swear--
I swear to fucking God,
you are so--
What? What? What?
I'’m so fucking what?
Say it. What am I?
Tell me, I am so fucking...
You'’re fucking psycho!
- Oh, yay!
- Yeah!
- Psycho!
- It'’s out of the bag!
You'’re fucking crazy!
I'’ll show you crazy!
- You want to fucking see crazy?
- Stop it! Stop it!
- What are you doing?
- Is that crazy enough for you?
- Is that fucked up? Huh?
- Stop it!
- Is that crazy enough for you?
- Yes, that is crazy,
you fucking psycho!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I'’m fucking driving.
-  Fucking hate you!
- Good! Good!
'’Cause I fucking hate you, too.
I fucking--
You crazy bitch.
Ah, you psycho bitch!
Oh, you'’re gonna cry.
Are you gonna cry now?
Is that your thing? "Oh, God!"
Oh, you look so fucking ugly
when you cry. It'’s horrible.
I can'’t-- Ew, I can'’t--
"Oh, help me, God!"
What the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
[Paul] Jesus! Oh, my God!
It'’s okay, it'’s okay.
Everything'’s fine. Hey, hey.
You'’re okay.
You have a mild concussion.
Where am I? Where am I?
Harvest Moon.
It'’s a private wellness clinic.
You fainted and hit your head.
We found you lying
on your living room floor,
unconscious.
The doctor said
you were sleep deprived
and extremely dehydrated.
No, no, no, that'’s not--
That'’s not--
That'’s not what happened.
Joshua, could you go
find Dr. Fowler
- and let him know Skye'’s awake?
- Of course, yeah.
I hope you'’re
feeling better, Skye.
I, uh... I brought a sweatshirt
for you, just in case you...
...you get cold.
We can cover that with makeup.
And the team'’s already working
on a fill piece for your hair.
Don'’t worry, you won'’t be able
to tell the difference.
And I'’ve cleared your schedule.
So today you can
just have a whole day
of rest and recuperation.
Where'’s my phone?
- I need my phone.
- It'’s right here.
I got it.
- I need it. Give it to me.
- Maybe later.
Right now, we'’re just
gonna focus on relaxing.
Mom.
Please, please.
Something really crazy
is happening to me.
I need to get out of here
right now.
No. We are gonna
stay here together
until we head to the venue
tomorrow for the preshow.
That way we can make sure
you'’re a hundred percent
and ready to perform.
No, no. I can'’t. I--
Can'’t what?
I can'’t do the show.
If you... cancel the show,
then you will be
checking yourself into
a recovery program.
That'’s the only
explanation... Mom--
...as to why Skye Riley
is canceling another tour
the night before it starts.
You will have to explain
to the label
who'’ve invested
millions of dollars.
And you'’re putting the workers--Mom, you don'’t understand!
No! You don'’t
understand, Skye.
There are
no more second chances.
If you cancel, this is it.
The media will rake you
over the coals.
We'’ll be sued
by the label for millions.
It will be the end
of everything we'’ve built.
Oh, my God, Mom.
Why is that
all you care about, Mom?
You treat me like
I'’m some fucking windup toy.
You don'’t give a shit about me!
How dare you
talk to me like that?
You arrogant little asshole!
I have given up
everything for you!
Every second of my time.
Years of my life.
My career.
And here I am,
sacrificing every fiber
of my being to support you.
But you'’re too selfish
to even see it.
You put everyone
through absolute hell,
and still we support you.
But you want to go
and throw it away? Fine!
Do it! Throw it away!
I don'’t care!
That'’s what everyone expects
of you anyway.
I wish you could feel
what it'’s like
having to live inside my head.
I'’ve tasted
what'’s inside your head!
No, no, please, no!
Please, no.
No.
No, no, no! Please!
No!
Oh, no, no!
Look what you'’re doing
to your poor mother.
No, God!
Oh, God, that'’s not real.
It'’s not real. It'’s not real.
It'’s not real.
No, no.
No!
It'’s not real, it'’s not real,
it'’s not real.
Oh...
Oh!
It'’s Joshua!
I need a second!
I'’m changing.[Joshua] Oh! Sorry! Uh...
You know what?
I'’ll wait out here.
Also, the doctor said
he'’s gonna come and see you
in a few minutes.
Actually, I...
I... I feel kind of thirsty.
I need a--
Do you think you could go
find me something to drink?
Oh. Uh, I brought
some bottles of water.
Put them
in the little refrigerator.
I feel like soda. Could you
get me a soda, please?
Sure. Yeah, no problem.
What kind?
Any kind, just... surprise me.
You got it. You know what?
I'’ll be right back
with one, uh...
surprising soda.
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck!
Fuck. Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Skye?
Are you--
Oh, my God! Is that...
blood?
No.
Hey, uh...
We need a doctor over here!
-  Shut the fuck up!
- Yeah, could we please
get some help, somebody?
- Just shut the fuck up!
- Are you hurt?
Somebody please help!
We need a doctor.
Oh, my God, Skye.
Hey... you, you, you!
Please help me!
Whoa, whoa, easy!
I got you.
Get away from me!
Hey... just take it easy.
I said get the fuck
away from me!
I'’m sorry. I'’m sorry.
Skye?
Skye? What are you doing?
Think about the tour.
Fuck the tour!
Is that Skye Riley?
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Oh, God.
Skye?
What are you doing out here?
Gemma, what are you doing here?
Your mom called me.
Are you bleeding?
- Is your car here?
- No, your mom'’s driver
drove me, why?
- Where is he?
- He just dropped me off
over there. What'’s going on?
Skye!
Skye Riley. That'’s her!
What happened?
Hey, that'’s Skye Riley!
Totally off her rocker.
Hey, get out! I need your car!
Ms. Riley, what--
Get the fuck out of the car![bystander 3] She'’s got a gun!
What the fuck are you doing?
Gemma, I love you,
but if I don'’t leave right
now, I'’m gonna fucking die!
Fuck it!
- I'’m coming with you. Move over.
- No, Gemma, no!
You don'’t know how to drive.
- Move over!
- Fuck!
[bystanders] Whoa!
Dude, where are we going?
What am I doing?
Where am I going?
- Where am I going? Skye!
- I don'’t know yet.
- Just keep driving.
- No, I need you to explain
what the hell is going on.
I need to get to Staten Island.
What? Gross. Why?
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
Jesus Christ!
You need to go to a hospital!
No! I need to go
- to Staten Island.
- What the fuck is going on?
Why are we going
to Staten Island?
Skye.
- Gemma, pull over, please.
- What? You just told me
to go to Staten Island!
Gemma, just fucking
pull over, please!
All I'’ve ever done
is make your life hell.
I don'’t deserve you.
So please, just pull over
and get away from me so
I don'’t fuck up your life, too.
No, fuck that noise.
Ride or die, bitch!
I need to...
I need to tell you something.
What?
Skye?
Hello?[Gemma] Hey, it'’s me.
I got your voicemail.
Sorry it'’s taken me a few days
to get back to you.
But, honestly,
I wasn'’t even sure
if I was gonna call you back.
Did you spend the night
at my place?
What? I haven'’t been
to your place in like a year.
Since you said I was
a "stupid opportunistic cunt,"
remember?
Also, what'’s up with these
weird-ass fuckin'’ text messages
you'’ve been sending me?
Hello?
Gemma hates you, Skye.
No, please. Please, Gemma, no.
Please, Gemma, no.
Not you, please.
No, no!
No! No! No!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, fuck you!
Let me the fuck out!
- Let me go!
- No one cares about you.
This is not real.
You'’re not driving,
you'’re not driving.
this isn'’t happening.
You'’re in my head,
you'’re in my head.
You'’re in my head!
You'’re not in control. I am!
You'’re not in control. I am.
I'’m in control,
I'’m in control, I'’m in control.
I'’m in control, I'’m in control,
I'’m in control.
Fuck you!
Learn to fucking drive!
Jesus Christ!
Christ, are you okay?
Where are your shoes?
I don'’t have any.
- Here, take this.
- Why do you have a gun?
Just take it! Hey!
If this theory of yours
doesn'’t work
or you see me change
and start smiling,
- shoot me in the head.
- Whoa, whoa, hold on!
Hey! You need to stop it,
no matter what.
We'’re going to.
- Promise me!
- All right!
All right, I promise
I'’ll shoot you.
How do we stop my heart?
Sorry I haven'’t
done anything about the lights.
- Is this a Pizza Hut?
- It'’s the only thing I could find
for lease on short notice
- that had a large enough freezer.
- Why do we need a freezer?
For your brain.
Fuck.
Once we stop your heart,
your brain stops
receiving oxygen.
Normally,
necrosis sets in immediately.
You'’d have two minutes maybe
before permanent brain damage,
but if we bring your body
temperature down far enough,
we can delay the process,
giving us up to nine minutes
before permanent damage.
We need to make sure this thing
isn'’t able to hang around.
And...
...I like our odds
with nine minutes better
than two.
The freezer door latch
is broken.
If it closes all the way,
it can'’t be opened
from the inside.
Here. Change into this.
Jesus, that'’s a lot of blood!
Are-- Are the cops
gonna be looking for you?
I don'’t know.
Let'’s just do this.
Once your body temperature
drops low enough,
I will inject you with a drug
that will cause your heart
to start slowing down
until it stops.
How long will it take?
It'’s critical you reach
flatline as fast as possible.
So I'’ll need to inject it
directly into your
internal jugular.
After 30 seconds...
you'’ll be dead.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Jugular, like in my neck?
Let me see the needle.
What the fuck, man?
I know. Sorry.
Lie down here.
Oh, my God,
I'’m so fucking cold.
That'’s the idea. I'’ll be
monitoring your heart rate.
The moment you flatline, I'’ll
start a timer for eight minutes.
Once the timer'’s up,
I will inject a dose of
adrenaline into your heart
and start CPR resuscitation.
I can'’t believe I might die
in the freezer of a fucking
Pizza Hut.
I promise
I'’m gonna bring you back.
Morris?
I'’m sorry about your brother.
I know that'’s why
you'’re doing this.
Thank you for helping me.
Can I ask what made you
change your mind?
Every good thing in my life...
ends up broken because of me.
I hurt everything
and everyone I touch.
It doesn'’t matter
what happens to me anymore.
But I will not
let this fucking thing...
use me to hurt anyone else.
Put this in your mouth.
Don'’t move.
I just have to get something.
Wait. Where--
Where are you going?
Shit.
Wait.
Morris?
Hey!
Don'’t leave me alone here!
Please.
Mor-- Morris?
No!
No! No!
I'’ve been waiting for you
for such a long time.
Mor--
Morris! Morris, it'’s in here!
Morris can'’t help you anymore.
It'’s just you and me.
I like wearing your skin.
You can'’t get away
from me, Skye.
You'’ll never
escape who you truly are
on the inside.
Look at me!
Fuck... you!
Skye!
Skye! Skye!
This isn'’t real, Skye.
No! No!
No.
No. No!
Please, no!
You'’re not in control, Skye.
No!
I am.
Break a leg out there.
No. No.
Skye, I love you!
Skye!
Whoo! Skye!
Skye, you'’re the best!
Skye!
I love you, Skye!
Skye, you look beautiful!
All right, Skye!
Skye![fan 2] Skye!
Whoo!
Yeah![fan 2] Skye!
I love you, Skye!
Smile.
No.
No!
Somebody help her!
[fan 7] My God. Do something!
I love you!
Get up, Skye!
Yeah! There you go, Skye!
Whoo! We love you, Skye!
All right, Skye!
[fan 7] Skye, we love you!
Yeah, Skye! You got this!
Whoo! Yeah, Skye!